A Finding Aid to the Robert Smithson and Nancy Holt Papers, 1905-1987, bulk 1952-1987, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Project Files, circa 1950s-1982; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 6.5 Linear feet Boxes 4-5, Boxes 17-18, OV 20, OV 22-26, OV 36, RD 28-30, RD 32-35
  - "Mud Pool Project", circa 1960s-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - New Jersey Projects, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 45)
    Oversized material digitized in Box 17, Folder 10.
  - New Jersey Projects, Oversized, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - New Jersey Projects, Chain Letter, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - New Jersey Projects, Map of Broken Glass, Atlantis, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - New Jersey Projects, Mirror Trail, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - New Jersey Projects, Mirror Wedge, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - New Jersey Projects, Urination Map of the Constellation Hydra, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - New Jersey Projects (Urination Map of the Constellation Hydra) Oversized, digitized with Box 4, Folder 50, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - "Non-Site #2 (Based on Weehawken Quadrangle Map, New Jersey-New York", 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - "Non-Site #3, Indoor Earthwork - Rock Fragments from Franklin, New Jersey" (Franklin Mineral Dump), 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - "Non-Site #3, Indoor Earthwork - Rock Fragments from Franklin, New Jersey" (Franklin Mineral Dump), 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - "Non-Site #3, Indoor Earthwork - Rock Fragments from Franklin, New Jersey" (Franklin Mineral Dump), 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - "Non-Site #3, Indoor Earthwork - Rock Fragments from Franklin, New Jersey" (Franklin Mineral Dump), Maquette, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Non-Site, California-Nevada (Double Non-Site), 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Non-Site, California-Nevada (Double Non-Site), Oversized, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 22, Folder 4)
  - Non-Site, California-Nevada (Double Non-Site, Baker Lava), 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Non-Site, California-Nevada (Double Non-Site, Obsidian Site), 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Non-Site, California-Nevada (Double Non-Site, Sand and Gypsum Site), 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Non-Site, Essen Soil and Mirrors, Essen, Germany, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Non-Site, Essen Soil and Mirrors, Essen, Germany, Oversized digitized with Box 4, Folder 60, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Non-Site, Line of Wreckage, Bayonne, New Jersey, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Non-Site, Line of Wreckage, Bayonne, New Jersey, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Non-Site, Line of Wreckage, Bayonne, New Jersey, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Non-Site, Line of Wreckage, Bayonne, New Jersey, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Non-Site, Line of Wreckage, Bayonne, New Jersey, Oversized, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 22, Folder 5)
  - Non-Site, Line of Wreckage, Bayonne, New Jersey, Oversized, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Roll 33)
  - Non-Site, Mono Lake, California, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Non-Site, Mono Lake, California, Oversized, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Non-Site, Mono Lake, California, Oversized, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Roll 33)
  - Non-Site, Palisades, Edgewater, New Jersey, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Non-Site, Palisades, Edgewater, New Jersey, Oversized, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Non-Site, Pine Barrens, New Jersey, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Non-Site, Pine Barrens, New Jersey, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Non-Site, Pine Barrens, New Jersey, Oversized, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 22, Folder 6)
  - Non-Site (Mica), Portland, Connecticut, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Non-Site, (Slag), Oberhausen, Germany, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Non-Site, (Slag), Oberhausen, Germany, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Non-Site, (Slag), Oberhausen, Germany, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Non-Site, (Slag), Oberhausen, Germany, Photographic Material, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Non-Site, (Slag), Oberhausen, Germany, Photographic Material, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Non-Site, (Slag), Oberhausen, Germany, Photographic Material, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Non-Site, (Slag), Oberhausen, Germany, Photographic Material, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Non-Site, (Slag), Oberhausen, Germany, Photographic Material, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Non-Site, (Slag), Oberhausen, Germany, Photographic Material, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Non-Site, (Slag), Oberhausen, Germany, Photographic Material, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Non-Site, (Slag), Oberhausen, Germany, Oversized digitized with Box 5, Folder 10, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Non-Site (Slate), Bangor, Pennsylvania, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Partially Buried Woodshed, Kent State University, Kent, Ohio, 1969-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Partially Buried Woodshed, Kent State University, Kent, Ohio, 1969-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Partially Buried Woodshed, Kent State University, Kent, Ohio, 1969-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - "Predictable Model for Unpredictable Project", circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Proposal for Earthworks and Landmarks, Dallas-Fort Worth Air Terminal, Texas, 1967- 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Proposal for Earthworks and Landmarks, Dallas-Fort Worth Air Terminal, Oversized, 1967-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Proposal for Earthworks and Landmarks (Dallas-Fort Worth Air Terminal) Blueprints, Oversized, 1967-1969; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 23, Folder 1)
  - "Proposal for Seven Aerial Pavements", circa 1960s-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - "Proposal for the Detection of Approximate Period Quality", circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - "Proposal for the Venezuelan Exposition Art in the Wilderness", circa 1960s-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Proposed Mining Reclamation Projects, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Proposed Mining Reclamation Projects, Correspondence, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Proposed Mining Reclamation Projects, Printed Material, 1964-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Proposed Mining Reclamation Projects, Photographic Material, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Proposed Mining Reclamation Projects, Photographic Material, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Proposed Mining Reclamation Projects, Oversized, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - "Pulverizations", 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Quicksand Pool, Alfred, New York, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Quicksand Pool, Alfred, New York, Oversized digitized with Box 5, Folder 34, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - "Short Description of Two Mirrored Crystal Structures", circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Six Stops on a Section, New York - New Jersey, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Six Stops on a Section, New York - New Jersey, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Six Stops on a Section, New York - New Jersey, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Six Stops on a Section, New York - New Jersey, Oversized, 1968-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Six Stops on a Section, New York - New Jersey, Oversized, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 23, Folder 2)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Correspondence, 1970-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Land Certification Forms (Blank), 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Notes, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Notes for Film, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Writings, "Spiral Jetty" Draft, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Writings, "Spiral Jetty" Typescript, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Writings, "Spiral Jetty" Proof, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Maps and Guides, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Maps and Guides, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Printed Material, 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Printed Material, About Spiral Jetty, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Photographic Material, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Photographic Material, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Photographic Material, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Photographic Material, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Oversized, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Spiral Jetty, Great Salt Lake, Utah, Oversized, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 23, Folder 3)
  - Spiral Jetty, Oversized, 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Roll 34)
  - Tailing Pond, Creede, Colorado, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Tailing Pond, Creede, Colorado, Oversized, 1967-1973; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 23, Folder 4)
  - Yucatan Projects, Yucatan, Mexico, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Yucatan Projects, Yucatan, Mexico, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Yucatan Projects, Yucatan, Mexico, Oversized, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified Project, Brooklyn Museum, Brooklyn, New York, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Unidentified Projects, circa 1966-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Unidentified Projects, Oversized, circa 1966-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified Projects, Oversized, undated; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 24, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified Projects, circa 1966-1973; Archival Resource Key (Roll 29)
  - Unidentified Proposed Project Maps, circa 1960s-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Miscellaneous Research Material, Images, circa 1950s-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Miscellaneous Research Material, Images, Oversized, circa 1950s-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Research Material, Maps, circa 1950s-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 61)
    Oversized material housed in OV 20, OVs 24 - 26, OV 36, RD 30, and RD 35
  - Miscellaneous Research Material, Maps, Oversized, circa 1950s-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 20)
    Oversized material from Box 5, F61
  - Miscellaneous Research Material, Photographs, circa 1950s-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Miscellaneous Research Material, Text, circa 1950s-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Miscellaneous Research Material, Maps (Antique and Arizona), Oversized, circa 1950s-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 24, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Research Material, Maps (Delaware, New Jersey, Ohio), Oversized, circa 1950s-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 25)
  - Miscellaneous Research Material, Maps (Maryland, North Carolina, Virginia), Oversized, circa 1950s-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 26)
  - Miscellaneous Research Material, Maps (Topographic), Oversized, circa 1950s-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 36)
  - Miscellaneous Research Material, Maps, circa 1950s-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Roll 30)
  - Miscellaneous Research Material, Maps, circa 1950s-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Roll 35)
- Personal Business Records, circa 1967-1970s; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 4 Folders Box 5
  Personal business records include gallery related loan arrangements and receipts for miscellaneous art supplies.
  The series has been arranged alphabetically by organization.
  Series is partially digitized; only a sample of the 92 receipts, all for Max's Kansas City in New York City, have been digitized.
  - American Federation of Arts, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - John Daniels Gallery, circa 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Receipts, circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Receipts, circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Financial Records, 1962-1972; Series 7; Archival Resource Key; 1 Linear foot Box 6
  Financial records include tax forms and preparation documents, including cancelled checks, receipts, statements, and related correspondence.
  The series has been arranged chronologically by document type.
  This series has not been digitized.
  - Cancelled Checks, Holt, 1964-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1-7)
  - Cancelled Checks, Smithson, 1962-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8-13)
  - Receipts, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
  - Stocks, 1964-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16-21)
  - Stocks, 1964-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Tax Documentation and Forms, 1963-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3-9)
  - Tax Documentation and Forms, 1968-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10-15)
- Printed Material, 1955-1985; Series 8; Archival Resource Key; 5.6 Linear feet Boxes 7-11, Box 18, RD 31
  Printed materials include books, clippings, and periodicals related to Smithson, either containing writings or sketches by him, or containing articles reviewing his work. While some of the clippings review Smithson's exhibitions and work, the bulk of the clippings are on the general topics of contemporary art trends, earth art, and emerging artists.
  Exhibition announcements and catalogs are of Smithson's group and solo shows from 1959 to 1985, and include the following concept exhibitions whose catalogs were issued in very limited numbers: One Month (organized by Seth Siegelaub, March 1969), Letters (organized by Philip Simkin, July 1969), Projects Class (Nova Scotia College of Art and Design, Fall 1969), and Exhibition 557,087 (organized by Lucy Lippard, 1969).
  Other rare printed materials in the series include Vito Acconci's Transference: Roget's Thesaurus, Acconci's periodical 0 to 9 (#6, July 1969), and the avant-garde periodical Aspen (#8, 1970).
  Also included are inventory lists of the published books, periodicals, and phonographs from Robert Smithson's library that have been transferred to off-site storage.
  The series has been arranged by publication type.
  This series has been partially digitized. For books and booklets, only the covers and title pages and/or other relevant pages referencing Smithson have been digitized. Some overized printed material has not been digitized due to size.
  - Book, Album 9-68. 2-71, ed. by Instituto Grafico Tiberno, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Book, Arte Povera, by Germano Celant, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Book, Breakthrough Fictioneers, ed. by Richard Kostelanetz, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Book, Essaying Essays: Alternative Forms of Exposition, ed. by Richard Kostelanetz, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Book, Great Western Salt Works, ed. by Jack Burnham, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Book, Handbook of the Collections: Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Book, If I had a Mind ??? (Ich Stelle Mir Vor), by Klaus Groh, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Book, Metro 14, ed. by Alfieri, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Book, Report on the Art and Technology Program of the Los Angeles Museum of Art 1967-1971, by Maurice Tuchman, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Book, Robert Smithson: Sculpture, ed. by Robert Hobbs, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Book, Transference: Roget's Thesaurus, by Vito Acconci, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Book, Writings of Robert Smithson, ed. by Nancy Holt, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Booklet, "Pamphlet of Essays Occasioned by an Exhibition of Painting at the Guggenheim Museum", 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Booklet, "Reclamation Works", 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Booklet, "Whitney Review", 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Clippings, circa 1955-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Clippings, 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Clippings, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Clippings, 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Clippings, by Robert Smithson, 1963-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Event Announcements, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Event Announcements, Hayden Planetarium, "Domain of the Great Bear," Press Releases, circa 1955- 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Event Announcements, Hayden Planetarium, "Domain of the Great Bear," Photographs, circa 1955-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Event Announcements, Hayden Planetarium, "Domain of the Great Bear," Photographs, circa 1955-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1960-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1967 January-April; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1967 May-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1968 January-May; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1968 June-September; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1968 October-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1969 January-February; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1969 March; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1969 March; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1969 April; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1969 May-June; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1969 July; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1969 August-September; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1969 September; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1969 October-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1969-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1969-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1970 January-July; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1970 August-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1971 January-April; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Exhibition Catalog, Oversized, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1971 May-June; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1971 July-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs (Documenta 5), 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1972 January-June; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1972 January-August; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1972 September-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Exhibition Announcements, Oversized, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Roll 31)
    Oversized materials from Box 10, F6 and F16
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 14)